Hold on, sir. I
'll take your period, sir.
Ma'am, you don't need to ask all this
.  Please take it generously.
Come to class.
Is your period due today?
It's better.
Okay, come to class then.   Please, please   After
hearing all that, I bought everything for the class
.
Sir, what are you thinking?   Just to
play catch.  Go ahead and
improve that chemistry
.
Hey, what are you going to do in the country?   Just
read, then
you'll know four or five words.  Chemistry ma'am, just a
minute.
Tell me, sir.
Where are you going in such a hurry?   I just went to
a meeting in Argentina
.
It's nothing else.  We have our PT
class today.  Take it yourself
.
Okay, thank you, sir.  [Music]
I don't understand a single thing, sir.
Why are you putting chemistry behind all the pretty girls?
So what did you
get?  That's what I'm asking, sir.
get from them?
Hey, let's have some tea.  Thanks.
[Music]